<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>The REC_USE_LIM field for indicator 7-1-2, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en">&lt;p&gt;Comparisons of the results from the 2007 CSES with previous surveys in 1993/94, 1996, 1997 and 1999, are not recommended due to differences in the survey design. Fieldwork from the last five surveys (2004, 2007, 2008, 2009 and 2010) covered 15 months, and results can be reported for both 12 month (calendar year) and 15 month periods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The weights used in the reports from CSES 2004, are adjusted by using the preliminary population projections which give over estimated population counts. The weights in CSES 2007 are adjusted by using the preliminary result from 2008 Population Census. Some provinces were excluded, due to cost and other reasons, in the sample for 2007. The estimates are however, adjusted for the under coverage error caused by excluding those provinces. A recalculation of the weights in CSES 2004 has been made for the coming analyses to obtain higher comparability between CSES 2004, and the surveys conducted from 2007 and onwards.&lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="km">&lt;p&gt; ការប្រៀបធៀបលទ្ធផលពីស៊ីអេសអេស ២០០៧ ជាមួយនឹងការស្ទង់មតិកាលពីលើកមុនក្នុងឆ្នាំ ១៩៩៣/៩៤, ១៩៩៦, ១៩៩៧ និង ១៩៩៩ មិនត្រូវបានណែនាំទេដោយសារភាពខុសគ្នានៃការរចនាស្ទង់មតិ។ ការធ្វើស្រែពីការស្ទង់មតិ ៥ ចុងក្រោយ (២០០៤, ២០០៧, ២០០៨, ២០០៩ និង ២០០៩) មានរយៈពេល ១៥ ខែហើយលទ្ធផលអាចត្រូវបានរាយការណ៍ទាំង ១២ ខែ (ឆ្នាំប្រតិទិន) និងរយៈពេល ១៥ ខែ។ [៣៣៨]
[៣៤៣] ទំងន់ដែលត្រូវបានប្រើក្នុងរបាយការណ៍ពីស៊ីអេសអេស ២០០៤ ត្រូវបានកែសំរួលដោយប្រើការប៉ាន់ស្មានប្រជាជនបឋមដែលអោយចំនួនប្រជាជនប៉ាន់ស្មាន។ ទំងន់នៅស៊ីអេសអេស ២០០៧ ត្រូវបានកែសំរួលដោយប្រើលទ្ធផលបឋមពីជំរឿនប្រជាជនឆ្នាំ ២០០៨ ។ ខេត្តមួយចំនួនត្រូវបានគេដកចេញដោយសារថ្លៃដើមនិងមូលហេតុផ្សេងទៀតក្នុងឧទាហរណ៍សម្រាប់ឆ្នាំ ២០០៧។ ទោះយ៉ាងណាការប៉ាន់ស្មានត្រូវបានកែសំរួលចំពោះកំហុសដែលគ្របដណ្តប់ដោយបណ្តាលមកពីការមិនរាប់បញ្ចូលខេត្តទាំងនោះ។ ការគណនាឡើងវិញនូវទំងន់នៅស៊ីអេសអេស ២០០៤ ត្រូវបានធ្វើឡើងសម្រាប់ការវិភាគនាពេលខាងមុខដើម្បីទទួលបានការប្រៀបធៀបខ្ពស់ជាងរវាងស៊ីអេសអេស ២០០៤ និងការស្ទង់មតិធ្វើឡើងចាប់ពីឆ្នាំ ២០០៧ និងចាប់ពីពេលនេះតទៅ។
			</language>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
