<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<status>success</status>
	<message>All metadata fields for indicator 4-3-2, translated into all languages</message>
	<data>
		<languages>
			<language lang="en">&lt;p&gt;Goal 4. Ensure quality education, environment and equity and enhance lifelong learning opportunities for all people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;4.3. By 2030, ensure equal access for all men and women in vocational training and higher education, including universities&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;4.3.2. Overall rate of study in technical and vocational education and training programs (15-24 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every 2 years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ministry of Labor and Vocational Training&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1-Mr. Thovy Hsandy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2-Mr. CHOM Mom&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3- Mr. CHOUP Vannak&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4- Mr. KHEAV Solyna&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Department of Planning, Statistics and Legislation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;+855 97 88 66 062&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;thovyhsandy@yahoo.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Number of trainees, students attended technical and vocational education programs by age (15 to 24 years old) &quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Percentage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ministry of labor and Vocational Training will collect the data and report to Ministry of Planning every year. The report will be published as “MoLVT Annual Report” that can be found on website: &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mlvt.gov.kh&quot;&gt;http://www.mlvt.gov.kh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Methods collected through administrative data by Ministry of labor and Vocational Training (MoLVT). And, MoLVT will send the report to Ministry of Planning for compiling data and reporting&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Cambodia Voluntary National Review (CVNR) will be produced during four years by four reports; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CVNR 2015-2018, published on June 2019&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CVNR 2019-2022, published on June 2023&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CVNR 2023-2026, published on June 2027&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CVNR 2027-2030, published on June 2030&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt; Six months after data collection/compiling period&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ministry of labor and Vocational Training&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ministry of Planning will produce Cambodia VNR 2019, 2023, 2027, 2030 that can be found on website: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mop.gov.kh/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://www.mop.gov.kh/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Royal Government of Cambodia (RGC) has robust and conducive policy and regulatory frameworks to ensure affordable access and connectivity. RGC, development partners, and private sector has continued to target infrastructure, essentially roads, rail, bridges, ports, hydropower, solar farms, power transmission lines and irrigation systems. This has, to some extent, enabled garment factories to be shifted from the capital to rural areas, making it closer to labour source and relieving some burdens on urban infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The indicator aims to measure the percentage of trainee and student who have achieved the minimum learning outcomes in vocational education program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Number of trainees, students enrolled in TVET, aged 15-24 yrs devided by Population aged (15-24 yrs and multiply with 100&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ministry of labor and Vocational Training &amp; Ministry of Planning will validate the data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Planning has the statistic and report department to lead the data management, data assurance and data assessment from its own ministry and the Ministry of Labor and Vocational Training&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of labor and Vocational Training have the statistic and report department to lead the data assurance and data assessment from their own ministries&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of labor and Vocational Training have the statistic and report department to lead the data assurance, reporting format, reporting monitoring and quality checking before sending the report to The Ministry of Planning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This indicator can be disaggregated by sex, occupation, age, region and others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The difference may arise due to: a) discrepancies in data sources; b) ISIC Revision used by a country; c) informal employment; d) coverage of data source (geographical coverage, economic activities covered, types of establishments covered, etc.); e) working-age population definition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;National Strategic Development Plan – NSDP 2019-2013: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mop.gov.kh/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://www.mop.gov.kh/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;National Skills Development Policy (NSDP): https://www.ilo.org/dhaka/Whatwedo/Projects/WCMS_226500/lang--en/index.htm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SDG Goal Knowledge Platform: &lt;a href=&quot;https://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/memberstates/cambodia&quot;&gt;https Cambodia Voluntary National Review 2019:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/content/documents/23603Cambodia_VNR_SDPM_Approved.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/memberstates/cambodia&quot;&gt;https://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/content/documents/23603Cambodia_VNR_SDPM_Approved.pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/memberstates/cambodia&quot;&gt;Ministry of Laboure and Vocational Training: &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mlvt.gov.kh&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/memberstates/cambodia&quot;&gt;http://www.mlvt.gov.kh&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/memberstates/cambodia&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/memberstates/cambodia&quot;&gt;://sustainabledevelopment.un.org/memberstates/cambodia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			</language>
			<language lang="km"/>
</languages>
</data>
</root>
